All right, I get the hint. You actually want
this class to be finished sometime before the next
Android release happens. We're almost done. So we look
in ForecastFragment in onStart. We've actually been cheating a
bit. Every single time we get to onStart, we
actually update the weather. Let's get rid of that.
It'll force us to actually have to use the
refresh function to get new weather, but it'll help illustrate
the cool stuff we're about to do with preferences.
We're going to stop cheating here. In onPreferenceChange, if we're
not actually binding preferences, we're going to execute a new
FetchWeatherTask if there's a change in location. Otherwise, we'll just
notify our CONTENT_URI to allow our cursor to update.
We still have to do one more thing. In ForecastFragment
we've been using an instance variable, mLocation, to save the
preferred location we get when we're actually an onCreate loader.
We've been doing that because we've been planning to
use this for a while. Let's override another function. In
onResume we need to check to see whether or not
our location has changed. So if our location is not
equal to null and Utility.getPreferred location does not equal
location, well, then we can call update weather. Let's see
what happens. You see it immediately changed back. You didn't
see that loading because it didn't have to load anything.
However, if we change settings to something else,
it's refreshing the background. Well, it turns out
updating weather doesn't actually help us here. Why?
Because our URI hasn't changed. Remember, we're doing
everything based upon URI. What we really need
to do is reset our loader. So, how
do we do that? Well, it's pretty straightforward.
Just like we did in onActivityCreated, we have to
use LoaderManager. So instead of calling updateWeather, what
we're actually going to do is call something else.
In this case, not an initLoader, but restartLoader.
It takes the same parameters as an initLoader. Now
let's try this again. That already looks better.
All right, let's change back to our own weather
again. And there we are. As you can see,
the weather is changing as we go from location
to location, but we still have this
problem. Obviously when we change settings here,
it doesn't affect anything, so we need to fix that. That's where you come in.